<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EyeCare</string>
    <string name="loginimage">LoginImage</string>
    <string name="eyecare">EyeCare</string>
    <string name="loginDesc">Check your eye disease with AI</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="registerAcc">Register?</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="registerDesc">Create new account</string>
    <string name="registerimage">registerImage</string>
    <string name="tagline">Your personal eye health companion</string>
    <string name="logo">Logo</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="analyze">Analyze</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string-array name="data_disease">
        <item>Crossed</item>
        <item>Uveitis</item>
        <item>Cataract</item>
        <item>Bulging</item>
        <item>Glaucoma</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_icon">
        <item>@drawable/crossed</item>
        <item>@drawable/uveitis</item>
        <item>@drawable/cataract</item>
        <item>@drawable/bulgingeye</item>
        <item>@drawable/glaucoma</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="data_desc">
        <item> The prisms lenses can alter the light entering the eye and reduce how much turning the eye must do to view objects. Vision therapy can help problems with eye movement, eye focusing and eye teaming and reinforce the eye-brain connection, Eye muscle surgery can change the length or position of the muscles around the eyes so they appear straight.</item>
        <item> eye drops with an anti-inflammatory medication, such as a corticosteroid. Eye drops to dilate the pupil and relieve pain. Wear sunglasses to protect your eyes if they are sensitive to light. Take a daily vitamin. Eat a healthy diet. Consult a doctor for further treatment</item>
        <item> Cataract surgery is the only way to remove cataracts and restore your clear vision. During cataract surgery, an ophthalmologist removes your clouded natural lens and replaces it with an intraocular lens (IOL). An IOL is an artificial lens that permanently stays in your and replacing it with a clear artificial lens. </item>
        <item>To address bulging eyes, several treatment steps can be taken. The use of
eye drops can help reduce irritation and keep the eyes moist. The doctor may
prescribe appropriate medications if the bulging is caused by infection, swelling,
or thyroid gland issues.

In some cases, surgery may be necessary to correct bulging that does not
resolve after other treatments. If the cause is unclear, a general practitioner
may refer you to a specialist for further examination.

When lying down, use a pillow to keep your head elevated to help reduce swelling.
Wearing sunglasses can protect your eyes if they are sensitive to bright light. If you
wear contact lenses, remove them and wear glasses to give your eyes a rest.</item>
        <item>Prescription eye drops can lower the pressure in your eye and prevent damage to your optic nerve. To lower your eye pressure, doctors can use lasers to help the fluid drain out of your eye. If medicines and laser treatment don’t work, there are several different types of surgery that can help the fluid drain out of your eye.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>